{
  "openingRemarks": "each operand between 6 and 9",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "\\(6 + 8\\)",
      "answer": "14"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8 + 6\\)",
      "answer": "14"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7 + 7\\)",
      "answer": "14"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9 + 8\\)",
      "answer": "17"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9 + 9\\)",
      "answer": "18"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8 + 9\\)",
      "answer": "17"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8 + 8\\)",
      "answer": "16"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6 + 7\\)",
      "answer": "13"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6 + 6\\)",
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7 + 6\\)",
      "answer": "13"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9 + 6\\)",
      "answer": "15"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7 + 8\\)",
      "answer": "15"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7 + 9\\)",
      "answer": "16"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6 + 9\\)",
      "answer": "15"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9 + 7\\)",
      "answer": "16"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8 + 7\\)",
      "answer": "15"
    }
  ]
}
